

CONTACT

Sulaimansyahjamal@gmail.com

6

+6285794309431

Cieksel 002/006, Selawangi Village, Tanjungsari District, Bogor Regency, 16840.

EDUCATION

AUG 2014 - AUG 2019 (INFORMATIC ENGINEERING)

Universitas Islam Negeri Sunan Gunung Djati Bandung (Islamic State University of Sunan Gunung Djati Bandung) 3.48

SKILLS

- Database(MySQL, Postgres)
- Golang
- RESTful Web Service
- Dart/Flutter (Hybrid App)
- MTCNA
- Network cabling, installation,
- Configuration and troubleshooting

SULAIMAN SYAH JAMAI

programmer

PERSONAL STATEMENT

I believe that my strong technical experience and education make me a highly competitive. With a B-Tech degree in Informatic Engineering, I have a comprehensive understanding of the full lifecycle for software development projects. Please, see my resume for additional info.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jun 2020 - present Enterprice Application Developer

PT Mitra Talenta Group

(Celerates)

Nov 2019 - Apr 2020 Flutter Mobile Developer

PT Semen Indonesia Beton by

Semen Indonesia

(Build App E-Commerce)

Jun 2017 - Oct 2019 IT Staff

Universitas Islam Negeri Sunan

Gunung Djati Bandung

(Network Engineer, maintenance

hardware networking, etc)

PCERTIFICATIONS AND LICENSES

May 2019 MTCNA

(Mikrotik)

ASSESSMENT RESULT

Taken Aug 2020 Attention to Detail

Result: Satisfactory

(This test unit measures the ability to identify patterns and inconsistencies in visual representations of data)

Taken Oct 2019 General Computer Knowledge

Result: Outstanding

Taken Oct 2019 HTML + CSS (Advanced)

Result: Satisfactory

(This is a pre-screening test for an experienced (1-2 years) developer's ability to use HTML and CSS for website layouts. It includes basic usage of CSS,

selectors and knowledge of CSS quirks.